Riley.
Hedda, that outfit looksamazing.
Well, they loved it at cityhall!
Yes, it's always impressive
when a priest wearsknock off Pucci.
What would you expect?Vatican drag?
No, but what'dthe groom think?
Why do you think they'reshipping heroff to Vermont?
Exactly.
Riley!
Hey guys, this ismy other half Riley
We've read all about youon Markus' blog.
Oh, how's the rash?
Yeah! Has it cleared it up yet?
Markus claims to have writer'sblock
but all he does is blog, blog,blog!
I didn't know you had awriter's block!
That's because he's hasn'tblogged about it.
I'm just a little stuck on mynew novel.
Oh, what's it about?
It's about a gay couplehaving a biological child.
So it's horror?
If we had kids,could you imagine
what we'd be doing right now?
Carpooling?
You blogged about my rash?
Sorry, honey.
Baby.
Hey Zeus.
Do you take change?
You cheap little bitch.
Sodomites, this is about me foronce!
First I wanna thank manhunt.net
for sponsoring my weddingreception.
Welcome!
You know, myrelatives wanted m e
to have a traditional ceremony.
Hello?!
You are my family!
You've been with me through itall:
Fat, thin. A horrible addiction
to very expensive handbags.
But now I've got Michael!
Where's Michael?
Where is my man?
Give me back my man!
Oh there you are!
Many of you are thinking
you're not gonna see me againafter today.
That I'm gonna disappear likeall
the fag hags of your youth.
Well, you're right
Finally I found a man who lovesme
and my pussy.
I said he loves my pussy!
And he's gonna tear it apart
behind that picket fence!
We love you Audrey!
Oh, I love you too
You know I lasted as long as Icould
with my boys.
Longer than any fag hag everhas.
Well .
Any except Violet.
Toss the bouquet already!
The bouquet is yours Violet, ifI had one.
He's working at the salontonight.
But you're still together?
Of course. Darian's perfect.
I actually think, I'm fallingin love with
Apparently Dan'scock is so hug e
that the only way to fit it inyour mouth
is to suck it while it’s soft.
Is that Beer Can Dan?
Yeah.
What about Darian?
Oh, Darian and Luke have anunderstanding.
Uh oh, cock-block.
Deflected!
Luke may have more experience
But his opponent is tenacious
It's battle of the bottoms.
And the biggest loser comes outon top!
Hey beautiful!
Hey Zeus, you beast!Look at ya .
Oh, I love it whenyou tease me !
So, I hear you and Luke arejoining forces.
Yes. God I love that guy.
He gave me his whole email listhe's getting sponsors
Oh, your benefit is going to beoff the hook.
New ink?
Yeah, check it out.
Ten years HIV positive, stillkicking.
You don't have to brandyourself.
I just want everyone to know
there is life after.
Well, I'll be with you insickness
and in health, count on it.
I love you.
Paparazzi!
Next Magazine
No more pictures!
You'll ruin their reputation.
I implore you, no photos!
Really, no more pictures.
I gotta go! See ya'!
Alright, we better go too.
Have a goodnight.
Hey, you too!
Dude!
What's with the skirt?
Violet?
Hey, I'm almost done.
I'm waiting behind the shrub.
Ok.
She's my roommate.
Yeah, you know man
that's a little weird actually.
Is she watching us?
She's harmless.
Fag hags, Jesus!
Hey!
More respect.
She's the last one
Welcome to Frisky Friends
where singles unite!
You have 3 new Frisky Friends!
Salome, you sound just like mymother.
Mother and I enjoy long countrydrives
Message deleted.
Next message.
Hi Salome, I'm looking for acommitted,
long term relationship with
Message deleted. Next message.
It's mailman.
I'm dying to get in a hotsession
before we meet.
Mr. Mailman.
It's Salome.
Got a delivery for me?
Another very big package.
What are you wearing?
Just two drops ofChanel Number 5.
Still off today?
You wanna chill?
Let's go to Coney Island
and ride the Cyclone.
Yeah,
let's do that.
So, how was Audrey's reception?
She was so happy.
I wish you could have been
there to see her face.
That's the one drawback
to owning my own business.
Not so much free time.
I have my own business
I think there is a little moreleeway
with roving sex parties.
I'm branching out
Can I use your salon for my
“Lazy Tops and Power Bottomsparty?
My host bailed after the policeraid
you know...
What?
You got hickeys again.
Oh, don't!
Who were you with last night?
Clearly an amateur.
Wait, let me get this right.
You watched two people
commit to one another,
Hooked up with some random
and then came crawling into bedwith me?
I took a shower first.
Come on D!
I got cock-matized
So, why'd you come over?
Because I wanted to sleep withyou.
But you had sex with somebodyelse.
It's not the same thing. Youknow that.
You are as bad as I am.
Was.
We met at a glory hole.
I know where we met.
I can’t do this anymore.
Wait a second...
You can't do this anymore?
Darian, we have anunderstanding.
Well, I asked for a newunderstanding.
If you can't give me that
I can't do this anymore.
Darian, come on. You know thatI
You know I
You know the impalas?In Africa?
Did you know they have liketwenty
sexual partners at a go?
And what's amazing is that notone impala
gets upset or angry
or says they can't do itanymore.
You're right!
I'm gonna take a shower
When I'm out,
I wanna find you gone, my keyson the table
and I don't want you coming
around here anymore.
It's over!
But I love you.
Hi, do you have a minute forfuture today?
Hi sir
do you have a minute for thefuture today?
Sorry, nope. I'm not breeding.
Are you my mailman?
Cute socks!
Salome? That's you.
My gay husband would kill forthese calves!
Please. We're in public.
Oh honey its New York-
Everything happens on thestreet.
So, Chinese is okay, right?
I can't do it.
I once had the worse gas
after a plate of mu shu pork.
I get it, where should we go?
No, I can't do this.
I'm gonna take a pass.
You're gonna pass?
I know I lied on Frisky Friends
but I came clean
I mean, I gave you my realstats.
Salome
I know this sounds cliché but
It's not you
It's me.
Really.
These were for you.
But I have experience
I have walked the catwalks inParis, Milan,
London!
In nothing but pasties.
Here, see?
My collection is designerclothing.
They were designer pasties.
Bradleigh, please
I need press, help me!
Please.
For the passion we shared
when we were boys?
Larice, are you threatening me?
Yes
So, you've seen the line sheet.
Bradleigh's new collection wasinspired by
the latest dinosaur discovered
down in Argentina.
Perfect! Let me know when
you want to come for the pull.
Okay.
Oh no, not again!
What is wrong with me, Riley?
Why do you keep saying that?
Nothing!
It's not you, it's him.
You are surrounded by men wholove you.
Love?
I deserver someone to love meand my pussy
Like Audrey.
Do you hear me?
Um, I hear you.
Donna I would, if I could.
I've got tools.
Not now, Donna.
Still got my hymen.
What you need Violet
is the male version of you.
A fag stag.
A metrosexual?
No, no no no no
A metrosexual will only throwyou off the scent
What is it Salome?
I'm going to lunch.
actually not lunch.
I'm being taken out forhigh-end water.
Can Violet cover reception?
One sec..
A fag stag is special.
He hangs out with gays becausehe enjoys
their energy andtheir attentio n
just like you do.
Does that sort of person reallyexist?
I don't think so.
Can I have a carrot?
Nevermind
I probably shouldn't.
My fuck buddy broke up with me.
Oh, no!
Really glad I never officiallymoved in
because then I'm not officiallykicked out right?
Sweetheart what happened?
Suddenly after three monthsDarian
is not a slut anymore.
What does he want? Monogamy?
Sounds like something
I need lasered off.
I know.
Oh my gosh, Luke.
I think it might be time for us
Please, don't say it.
Grow up.
I can hear that from anyone butyou.
But, maybe it's time.
I don't see what theproblem is ?
So I play around
what's that got to do withDarian?
But, you know I would give myheart
A lung, and what's left of myliver
to have a chance with a manlike Darian.
That means, you know how luckyyou are
Can I tell you what happened tome?
I met a frisky friend for lunchtoday.
And he can't put up with me fortwo minutes
I mean, leaves me onthe street ,
can you believe it?
I'm not even worth a lousylunch.
Which frisky friend?
What's his name and where doeshe live?
Why, what are you going to do?
Beat him up.
Not only a mailman, but aGemini.
Have you known me to stoop thatlow?
A Gemini!
Yeah, you dodged a bullet onthat one.
And he was probably bi-polar.All Geminis are bi-polar.
Hi baby!
Good to see you.
Look at that ass inthose jeans .
Thank you.
I have spammed my whole list.
Every last queen is going to be
at that benefit.
What about our queen mother?
Of course! I have alreadypoached some
last season Bradleigh for thesilent auction.
There is nothing I wouldn't do
to keep HIV stigma-free!
You should throw her on stage,she
Can revive her old high schooltap routine.
I do a mean Shim-Sham-Shimmy.
Oh really?
Let's see those moves baby.
Oh, no one wants to see mymoves,
when we can ogle yours.
Oh, that's not fair.
No, it's not fair at all!
Okay
next time I get dumped in thereal world
it's going to be by someone hotlike Zeus,
Not some bi-polar mailman.
Tell it, girl.
Why o why I can't find astraight man?
Why can't I?
Why don't you try a straightbar?
Who'll go with me?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying!
Okay, you don't need to goanywhere
We will find you a fag stag.
Riley is convinced that I'llfind straight man
masquerading around the gayworld.
Actually, a fag stag is urbanlegend.
Okay, but you haveabout an hou r
to find this mythical unicorn
before mama goes home for phonesex
She's not lying.
You know maybe Frisky Friends
is not the best way to meet aman.
It's a numbers game Markus
It's a numbers game
I'm just saying nomore Geminis .
How about the internet?
I talk better that I type baby!
Uh Oh, here comes the fuck mevoice
Look out!
Oh that feels so good
I love it on the right side ofmy
Tuna juice!
-Enough about the gash wound.-Thank you.
Stop calling my pussy a gashwound!
Okay.
Hey guys
Hey, what's going on?
Hello Goddess!
Hey sweetie.
So good to see you.
You too.
You guys have fun tonight.
Thank you.
Remember when Peter and Derekwere
looking for a surrogate fortheir gayby?
You know they asked Violet,right?
I'm like, HELLO!!
Entrance only, and still theypleaded.
I'm like find another womb!
How hard can it be?
Seriously half the world hasone!
Who did they find? Derek'ssister.
I understand it; someone else'segg
She's just a surrogate but
Don't you think it can catch
I don't know, incestby osmosis ?
That's beautiful.
What a beautiful gift of love
from Derek's sister.
It's not as if Derek could fallpregnant.
Well, he's been trying foryears.
Markus' new novel is actually
Is about a man who's giving abirth
Well it's about how life wouldbe different
if men could give birth.
Well, I'll tell you.
Abortion clinics on everycorner!
Oh, hold on!
Here comes the coat hangeragain.
I'm sorry, your balls are inthe way.
That's not funny!
That's not funny at all!
Your color is fantastic.
Who does it?
I was “Done by Darian .
Who hasn't been?
Darian
Yeah
Are you still gonna donate yourcoupon
for the silent auction Zeus isdoing?
Of course.
I also got couple of things foryou.
Stop by the salon alright?
I will.
How about the hottie right overthere?
You are so mean to me.
Wait, who's that?
Riley says that's my fag stag.
Unicorn
Sweet, thanks!
Cheers! Drinks on me.
Oh my God.
Salome. OH MY GOD!
Are you dead?
What happened to you?
You look Amazing.
Feed me!
Promise me you won'ttell anyon e
you found me behind a dumpster.
Okay?
Alright.
I am really worried.
When I don't eat, I get sleepy,okay?
Salome, you're naturally thin.
If I was you, I’donly be eatin g
And fucking.
Violet,
let me tell you something:
Fucking is overrated.
Guys line up around the blockto fuck me.
It is really tiresome.
There is a guy right here inthis diner
that wants to fuck me.
Who?
Black guy, Oscar Giovanniscarf, biceps.
He's behind you.
He doesn't know that he shouldknow
that I know he's cruising me,you know?
Wait.
He's actually cruising you.
Oh my god!
Just play aloof.
Violet!
Stop with the straw.
You lost him.
And you're gonna keep losingthem
until you get off your racket.
My racket?
Your racket is what's stoppingyou.
Well, I don't look like you.
It's not just your looks.
There is someone for everyone.
I believe that.
Thanks.
Let me ask you something.
where were you earlier?
Out with the boys.
Okay.
Do you know that story in thenews about
the family of peacocks that
took in the orphan elephant?
Oh, yes.
And then theelephant ran aroun d
thinking it was a peacock?
So sweet.
It's not sweet.
It's ridiculous.
Picture it!
Violet, you are not a peacock!
You are an...
Have you ever thought maybeyour gay
friends just don't wanna shareyou?
No.
They wanna keep you wrapped upin
their own little world
away from men who want women.
That's a horrible thing to say.
Do you wanna get married andhave kids?
No.
See?
The gays have totally warpedyour mind.
They do refuse to go tostraight bars.
And they are always insultingmy pussy.
But no, my friends want what Iwant.
Okay.
Okay what?
You're not willing to becoachable.
I am!
I'm coachable.
Then I can help.
God...
I ate so much.
I'm just gonna hit the ladies'room.
It might be a minute or two.
Just pick a number.
10,000 words a day.
I wish...
it's just that... you know
their baby is born and I'velost the plot
Maybe male mothers eat theiryoung.
Thanks, that's very helpful.
Baby!
Gays don't breed.
It's what separates us from theanimals.
We should invest in
valuable real estate instead.
Let's do that...
How about that rooftop
at Audrey's reception?
How about...
this valuable real estate, ha?Right here...
It's looking a bit neglected.
Seriously...
we're not breeders.
We don't have to worry about
the rest of the planet.
Global warming, recycling...
Oh, I would hate to recycle!
So why not write about that?
Because I'm writing a fantasy,Riley.
Your husband is an idealist.
Doll, I love you...
but I'm not your husband.
It's their word.
It could be our word.
Pear puree?
What's this?
Just research...
Okay...
I've got an idea...
I wanna take you out tomorrownight
for some solid food.
Cheer you up.
I love you.
I love my husband!
I love you
Ah... husband
Just found this at the fleamarket!
What do you think?
Cute, ha?
You can drape it
you can belt it, you can crimpit!
You can knock it off in China
for 50 cents pop.
Precisely.
Make that happen.
Remind me to give this splendorto
Donna when she gets back.
Oh hey!
Drinks tonight?
Markus has writers' group.
I have a dinner date tonight
and I don't plan on coming homeafter.
Not another frisky friend?
Why do you say it like that
"another frisky friend"?
What? You want me all toyourself?
Or what?!?
Wow!
That's beauty coupon for
a silent auction I'm doing
I just gave it to you.
Okay, thanks
I actually wanted to speak withDarian
about another matter...
I already told you Darian iswith a client.
Hey yo! Darian, hey!
Am I invisible?
Yeah, to me.
Darian listen, is now a badtime?
Now is good.
Okay, thanks so much for thiscoupon
Can we speak in private?
Since when do you care aboutprivate?
Okay.
Well D
I wanna invite you to a nicedinner or...
something romantic of yourchoice.
Um.. why?
Well, you know that story in abook
with Noah and ...animals and
Wait, wait, wait.. Noah's Ark?
And a bird brought Noah a twig
which meant everything is gonnabe okay.
So, you're here as...
as a twig?
I'm here to show you just howmuch
I want everything to be okayfor us.
Wow! Luke... thank you...
for that rare glimpse ofsincerity.
And thank you for stopping by...
But this is...
The rest of your stuff.. frommy apartment.
Don't... don't cry
You know you like that one...aah come on!
Good boy!
Put on there now... no, on topof it, ok?
Put it on there.
Little person.
Um... this is Joey.
Say hi Joey
Hey!
Ashley's sitter called insick...
Ashley?
My mentor from writers group
And how often does Ashley'ssitter
call in sick?
Oh... um.. just Fridays...
sometimes Wednesdays.
You couldn't tell me?
You know, sometimes you're notthat easy
to talk to aboutcertain things .
Not that easy to talk to...
Ashley's just running late..
she'll be here any minute.
Markus I just want what's bestfor us.
You know, to move up,get ahead ,
own some property.
You know this gig can help ussave.
Ashley set me up baby sittingfor others too.
I'm really good with kids,okay ?
Yeah, she's done wondersfor your writing..
Just look at Joey...
Isn't he adorable? Just look athim.
Oh, Joey baby
Welcome to the “Lazy Tops,Powe r
Bottoms party. Show me yourdick.
I just got to make sure you'renot the police.
Here's a bag for your clothes.
Welcome to the “Lazy Tops,
Power Bottoms party. $40please.
I'm on the list
Okay, what are you doing here?
I came to fuck my brains out.
Um.. in front of all thesepeople?
With all these people.
Okay, what the hell is going onhere?
You're deliberately trying tohurt me?
Take it easy, Luke...
Haven't you heard about theimpalas in Africa?
Hey sweetie!
Hi.
Frisky friend 265, Mike.
Hey!
Donnie and I work together
as flight attendants
Air hostesses!
Oh, yes.
In the unlikely events of waterlanding,
you're all gonna die!
That's nice!
I'll be back to get your ordersin a bit.
Okay.
Air hostess, ha?
Oh, my ticket out of Idaho.
I got some buddies out West...
That’s beautiful country.
Uh, beautiful yeah, but...
all anyone wants for you is
the same old stuff...get married, have kids.
I want something different.
Yeah, I hear you.
Yeah?
Yeah, we're an island ofmisfits.
I actually moved here to bearound
more open-minded women.
You still in thefriendly skies ?
No, I had to give it up.
Oh, after 9/11?
Oh, no!
I just kept ballooning up onthe plane food
No way.
Oh, yes way. I mean Donnie
Donnie used to have a 29 inchwaist
I mean I lost most of what Iput on,
I mean except for my fupa...
but I'm fine with it.
Umm, with what?
Fupa. Fat Upper Pussy Area.
But... it's a little fupa, ahappy fupa.
I would hate to see an angryone.
Oh yeah we can't have that.
Uh, what would you recommend?
The chicken cutlet here isexcellent.
But I would stay away fromcheese
tonight if I were you.
Why is that?
Clogs up your anal cavity.
I did not know that.
Oh, except for goat cheese.
You know there is some enzyme
that makes it okay.
This isn't good dinnerconversation, is it?
No, no, no... be yourself.
Um.. I hear zucchini is greatfor down there.
Most veggies are...okra is thebest.
I'm all about anal health.
Oh, me too.
It's just good manners.
So, are you kids ready?
Yes. I'll have the chickenfried steak, please.
Chicken fried steak, you sir?
Just a burger.
Burger.
No cheese!
Oh, that's work, I've gottatake this.
Okay.
Oh, sweetie he's fine!
I don't know why you're
bothering with dinner.
You're right put in that order,pronto!
I will honey, I will.
That was the best sex of mylife.
You're so high energy.
You want games?
I'll out-slut you in a second.
Hey, round two at my place?
This time, I'll doall the work .
What are you doing home?
You're supposed to be gone allnight.
Well, you're cleaning? It'sFriday.
Aren't you supposed to be
bringing queers together?
Well,
It smells like poppers in here
Where did you have your party?
The police raided our lastlocation.
So..
So?
No!
You got home before I could...
Is that shit on my bedspread?
That's not shit.
That is shit!
No, that isdefinitely not shit .
It's biss.
Biss?
Butt piss.
Oh God! That is so gross Luke,oh my god!
I'm sorry! Somebody must havegone
overboard with enemas.
I'm... I'm doing laundry now
Listen I was gonna tell you
but I thought maybe...
You thought maybe Iwould objec t
to a gay sex party in mybedroom?
That doesn't turn you on?
No, it does not turn me on.
That's the problem. I'm not oneof you.
Salome was right
I've just become way tooenmeshed
in your world.
Listen, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna wash everything...
It's OKAY because I'memancipating
myself from this...
Is that biss on thetable cloth ?
It's not my biss.
I don't care whose biss it is!
And he just left a twenty.Cheap fucker!
He walked out on you?
Just like that?
Were you being outrageous?
I may have been a littleoutrageous.
This is more than cosmetic
you know that, right?
Make-up can clear blemishes andstuff...
but not even top of the line
L'Oreal can fix a fucked upface.
And what we have here is afucked up face.
What are you saying?
I'm saying surgery.
You need to go under knife andkill
the fag hag inside.
Yes, okay. She's gone.
Just snip her out.
She's dead.
Great.
So what are you doing Thursday?
Going out with... friends.
It's our ritual.
It's your racket.
Are you coachable?
Yes, I'm coachable. What'shappening?
Well, a promoter friend of mine
is launching a new weekly partyThursdays
at Fine Feline.
Want to be my plus-one?
You want me to beyour plus-one ?
I celebrate diversity, you knowthat.
Plus I owe you one.
Salome wow I'm...
I'm very flattered.
I'm gonna have a table withbottle service
and everything.
Did you know Markus was running
a nursery out of our apartment?
Maybe.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why is nobody talking to me?
It's all on the blog.
And I'm not going to be able
to go out Thursday.
Why not?
Because you're a cock-blocker.
No, Riley.
It's because I'm never gonnaget what I want
if I keep repeating the same
patterns of behavior.
In other words... cock-blocker.
What should I wear on Thursday?
Uh.. okay let me see...
Let the pussy out of the bag...
Dress code: the cattier thebetter
Are you wearing a fucking catsuit?
Thank you very much.
Hey Violet!
Here kitty, kitty, kitty
Hey stop! Where are you goingso fast?
Home.
Isn't this the outfit you wore
to the fetish ball...2007?
Good memory.
Yeah, well I always notice you.
Oh, you might be the only one.
Careful!
Do you ever just feel like youdon't
belong anywhere?
Hello.
Why do you think I was so biginto heroin.
You're clean now, right?
Yes, two years.
Damn.
Look... Violet...
Before I came here, before youever knew
me, no one wanted a thing to dowith me.
I swear, not anyone.
Well, now we have all thesefriends
and they...
They love us.
They shower us with all thisattention
Yeah, I mean, that doesn't hurteither.
Well, attention doesn't sleepwith you
at night...
well, not with me.
Come here
It's alright.
Sorry.
No, it's not you. It's just...
I'm positive, you know.
It's just kissing.
Some people won't even share
the same spoon.
Some people are stupid.
Ah, I'm stupid.
Why am I kissing a gay boy?God !
I'm retired.
Retired?
I want to be wanted, Zeus.
It's not fair to me, okay?
This fruit fly is finished.
You have one new frisky friend.
Hi! Salome...
My dad owns the general store
of the Idaho town where I grewup.
He expected me to take it overbut I
came to New York to become anarchitect.
I'm Vern and I would love to
hear your story.
Vern?
Violet! Hey, are you home?
No.
Can we talk?
Are you on that phone lineagain?
No!
I need love.
Me too.
I miss Darian.
You try too hard, women don'tdo that.
I am just being myself.
Exactly. Stop it.
Now just close your eyes
and simply ask the universe.
The benevolent universe willalways
manifest what you need.
That's not true.
If I fall from a ten-storybuilding,
am I gonna manifest wings?
No. But you can manifest atruckload of
mattresses on the street below.
You watch too many cartoons.
What? It could happen.
Gerald?
Salome.
How are you gorgeous?
Can I get you a non-fat soylatte?
Yes... what a coincidence.
See Violet I was justmanifesting
a non-fat soy latte.
Fine Feline was major, ha?
So major.
Well, Violet didn't like it.
Not major.
Oh, cat-woman.
Go on Gerald...
Don't forget 16 splendas
and a stir-stick, thanks.
Voila.
Notice my lack of effort?
The lesson here is that theuniverse would
never tell you to put on apleather catsuit...
so don't try so hard next time,ok?
Oh, I'm not going back toFine Feline again.
You promised youwere coachable .
I'm gonna coach myself.
You can't coach yourself!
You'll never manifest a manthat way.
There's more then one way toskin a cat.
That's funny... not true.
But funny.
Yeah, when we meet, I'll takeyou
on a tour of lost gems.
I'm very sentimental when itcomes
to architecture.
I adore sentimental men, Vern.
We'll start with the Roxy.
The Roxy! You've been?
Spanish inspired interior, thesoaring
columns, it's rococo stylerotunda.
The Roxy had a rococo rotunda?
I really wish I could have seenit.
Oh my gosh, I used to go allthe time.
How? It was demolished in 1961.
The gay club?
No! The Roxy was amovie palace .
Where the Rockettes began.
The high-kicking, showgirlRockettes?
Originally they were theRoxy-ettes.
Oh, the Roxy.
You know there's a famousLife Magazine
shot of Gloria Swanson standingon the
rubble in a red boa as theytore it down.
Gloria Swanson in a red boa?
I have manifested a fag stag.
You manifested a fag.
Gloria Steinem neverwore a boa .
Gloria Swanson. Vern isstraight!
Bradleigh, do straight men knowwho
Gloria Swanson is?
Norma Desmond? Only if they'regay.
Come on!
Only gays obsess over faded,deluded,
once beautiful women.
We can relate.
See!
Climax Magazine is here.
Marjorie Max.
Violet, skedaddle.
Gentlemen.
Marjorie!
Right this way.
The inspiration for this seasonis
punk, Pocahontas andprehistoric.
Clever. I see we're intoalliteration.
This frill must be the“prehistoric.
Pterodactyl in heat?
More or less.
Ah, fur. You have no qualmsabout
killing these cute littlecritters?
Bradleigh says fur comes fromtrees.
Fir trees.
Look at me, pretending to care.
I just don't see how it fits tomy story.
I've seen you in Climax before.
I modeled for the magazineonce, yes.
Oh don't remind me, long timeago.
It was a matinee idol story?
Yeah.
This mug once was verylucrative.
And perfect for the "Daddy" inthis fall's
editorial shot byStephen Miser !
Stephen Miser? Oh be still mybeating heart.
What's the story?
I love Daddy!
But I'm not old enough to be aDaddy.
Tell you what.
You be Climax magazine's “Daddy
and I'll give Bradleigh's
prehistoric line somep-p-p-placement.
Get ready for your close up,Norma.
Do you have a minute for thechildren?
You have got to be kidding me!
Excuse me sir, do you have aminute
for the children?
Baby I'm home.
Jim had a hysterectomy.
Hey Violet is not coming toyour reading,
I think she's boycotting us.
I can't believe I had to givehim a
hysterectomy.
It's changed everything.
What?
Jim, in my novel.
Sorry for Jim.
How was your day, honey?
Oh great.
Bradleigh says you can join forour trip
to Taipei in November.
What trip?
Remember Bradleigh won
Designer of the Year in Taiwan?
Right. But, you knowin Novembe r
I'll be in edits.
Baby, you can bring yourcomputer to
Taipei. Come on, it'sall-expense paid
travel.
It'll advance my career.
A chance to forget babies
and hysterectomies.
Oh my God, don't remind me.It's so sad!
So, are you in?
Could we maybe swing by
Polynesia on the way to Taipei?
You know, Ashley showed me
this great new site.
There's not much red tape,
they make it so much easier.
What site?
Adoptakanakababy.com
Baby let's just check it out.No strings.
It might break up the monotonyof our lives.
The monotony of our lives?
Yeah. You know,maybe that's wh y
Violet is boycotting us. Changeis good.
Come on baby, relax.
Feels nice?
Yeah, come on.
What smell is that?
Baby oil.
Isn't it wonderful?
Polynesia is on the way toTaiwan, right?
No...
If you suck cock, hang up now.
If you think you might enjoysucking cock
in the future, hang up now.
Vern? Hello, Vern?
I'm not gay.
But you go to gay bars, right?
Why in the world would I dothat?
Oh, well I had to ask.
So, what’re you into?
What do you mean?
I mean, what are you passionateabout?
Well, what I do. Architecture.
I'm especially fascinated withcolumns.
Columns?
Wanna talk about thick, rockhard shafts?
What about them?
How about putting them up mychimney pot,
Mr. Architect. Yeah?
Then stucco my flying buttressto the wall!
Uh, Salome, I'm just a normalguy.
I can do normal.
I want to be up front and letyou know
I'm looking for a simple kindof woman.
That's me, I'm a simple girl.From Idaho.
My face is rural too!
I have an ample bosom and a...
well, my whole body is kind ofample.
I really wanna meet you and getfrisky but
if you're expecting some, Idon't know,
thin-hipped bitch who's gonna
I'm not!
You're not?
No, I want a keeper, Salome.
Me, too.
And it's Violet. I lied.
Well, we all fib on FriskyFriends.
So what's your real name?
I mean, I know it's not Vern.
No, it is Vern.
Oh, well you have a nickname oranything?
My parents call me Chippy.
So, Vern, what did you fibabout?
I don't know exactly but Iprobably did fib.
Now that I know your name,Violet,
do you still wanna meet?
Bethesda fountain. Same time?
10am and I'll be wearing red.
Red hot. Can't wait!
You did lie.
Oh I can't take it this!
Hello?
Vern you are a liar! I can'ttake this!
No, no I can't! I can't!
Help! Help!
Please! No, I just can't!
Get away from me you lunatic!
Everyone's a fucking freak.
I just can't deal with thisanymore.
Violet, is that you?
What are you doing down there?
Did you loose a contact orsomething?
Vern?
You must be Daddy.
Riley.
Hi, I'm Jenny. Matt's mom.
He looks like a complete angel,doesn't he?
Don't be fooled.
He's an absolutely unmanageablechild.
So was I.
You have kids?
I'm gay.
No, no kids.
Alright if you worked aStephen Miser set,
You know I don't wanna hearanyone,
I don't wanna see anyone
Unless it's through my lens.
Child. Love your Daddy, uhm?
Mr. Miser, I'm
Poof!
Matt?
No! I wanna stay with Riley.
Hey it's ok buddy, your mom andI, we're
gonna make plans. I promise.
Gotta go. C'mon hun. Sweetie!
The UN is the firstinternational building
in the US.
I suppose that concludes ourtour.
I loved it.
Should we go for drinks?
Why in the world would I wannado that
When I can be with you alone.
Do you go drinking a lot?
I wouldn't say that.
I may have partied a little inmy youth.
But that is behind me.
You're so beautiful.
Your place or mine?
You don't wanna gohome togethe r
on our first date?
No! uhm no!
Of course not.
I'm totally teasing.
Funny lady.
Come on. Let me walk you home.
Oh, baby you're home.
I'm almost ready.
So.
I checked outadaptakanakababy.com.
You did?
And?
And I didn't see anything
about refundsor exchanges.
I also never imagined in myentire gay life
that the topic of children
would ever come up.
Neither did I. But
I guess secretly
I hoped that it would.
What is that?
Markus
I love you
I want you to have everythingyou want.
Even if it's not what you want?
How will I know if we don't geta chance
to practice?
Oh my god.
You got me a Toy Pomeranian?
You wanted a Toy Pomeranian
since you were ten.
Well, that or a Chihuahua...
and you know how I feel aboutrats.
You've been reading my blog.
Oh, Thank you.
I thought you werean ex-Mormon ?
I left the church,
but I haven't beenexcommunicated.
Stick with me kid.
Wait a minute.
If you're not a Mormon, whycan't
you enjoy a glass of wine withme?
I don't like it.
You told me you've never had adrink.
I haven't.
How do you know you don't likeit?
Do I need to sleep with a man
to know I don't like it?
You know them?
Ah, co-workers.
Actually they are pretty great.
Uhm...we could go out with themsometime,
if you wanted to.
Where would we go?
We could go to a gay bar.
I think that'd be too muchanthropology
for this architect.
I told you I'm not very social.
Where do you go for fun?
To sleep.
I prefer to have my fun early.
I'm a big fan ofcolumn-watching.
Column-watching?
Yeah.
Tomorrow I'll be up before 5
to catch them at sunrise.
Holy fuck!
Sunrise?
Yeah, sunrise is my favoritetime of day.
Well, if you want to catch theworm.
Or if you wanna see Corinthiancolumns
come to life.
So, you just uh...
sit there and stare?
It's a form of meditation forme.
We all have our own way ofgetting centered
in this crazy city and that'smine.
Absolutely sweetie.
I mean whatever it takes.
You must think I'm freak.
Most people think I'm a freak.
No!
no, actually I don't.
And I think columns aremagnificent.
Do you wanna watchthem with me ?
You might have to sleep over ifyou did.
Check!
Oh, okay.
Have my babies, have my babies
What?
Just making sure the condom isstill on.
Of course it is.
Have my babies, have my babies!
Move to Idaho and have Chippy'sbabies.
Look.
Look now
Are you sleeping through this?
No, just resting my eyes.
Watch as the sun dances across
the granite at each new moment.
Watch.
Look, magic.
Hey! Guess what?
You got a dog.
-How'd you know?-Women know.
I also know that you werenever going to get a dog.
You have to bend over
and pick up the poop. Remember?
Baby makes Markus happy
so I've changed.
You called a dog Baby?
You are such a lesbian.
Markus named him
but thank you Donna.
How's the hymen?
You know my hymen -
hanging in there.
Come over tonight, meet Baby.
Oh, I can't.
Dinner with Vern.
Pre-game before Zeus' benefit
at Vlada?
Oh, that's Friday night.
Oh shit!
I have plans with Vern Fridaynight.
Vern, Vern, Vern.
Bring Vern.
Uhm
I don't think he's gonna wantto go.
We're all dying to meet him.
The timing is just not right.
I'm just not comfortable having
him know about my past.
What's wrong with your past?
Oh, please
don't take it personal.
You know the truth is
I don't even know if Vern's mytype.
So you'd rather be with himthan with us
for a cause you've alwayssupported?
Don't worry, I'll stop by.
You act like it'ssuch a burden .
I said I'll stop by, so leaveit alone.
Dating is stressful enoughwithout
this extra pressure from you,
and texts from Luke.
and these super pokes from
friends on Facebook I don'teven know!
Love,
Vern
It's tough being popular.
I'm gonna name my first bornDaisy.
It's that time of the month,huh?
I hate when men do that.
Why do men always say that?
Wow.
The billionaire that got away
used to send me pink daisies.
Letting him get away is thebiggest regret
of my life.
Not because we had anything incommon.
We didn't.
But it was this game he lovedcalled Snooker
What’s that?
I don’t really know.
And you point is?
My point is
I never bothered to learnSnooker
and now he’s on a yacht in theMaldives
with someone who did.
Was the sex good?
Standard missionary.
Vern, too.
Really vanilla.
We don’t have that much incommon, either.
Violet
this guy sends you flowers.
He actually likes you.
He does, he likes me.
So he’s got possibility.
And compatibility is notpossibility.
All you’ve got to do now
is fake interest in whatinterests him.
And then after that he’s yoursto mold
any old way you want.
Am I right Donna?
What the fuck do you want?
You should want this.
He’s boring.
Do you want to be loved,
or do you want to beentertained?
I wanna be entertained?
No, no, no!!
What happened to my veganwedding?
Yeah, okay
Yes, fine I stole yourstanky ass strap-on!
In a roundabout way,
Donna is supporting what I’msaying.
I doubt that.
And what are you saying?
Compatibility is notpossibility.
Violet
learn the Snooker.
You watching me?
Maybe
How are things going at thesalon?
Ahhdrama.
Had to fire my receptionist.
She was a bitch.
Yeah.
Shall we
call a truce
to the dueling sluts?
Maybe.
You’re here!!
Oh my god! Did you see thesilent auction?
No!
I made Markus put money on
Liza Minelli’s g-string.
And I’m winning!
You guys are bombed.
Open bar. Hello!
What can we get you to drink?
No, nothing I can’t be drunk
when I see Vern
Oh, sorry I missedyour reading .
Oh, that’s okay.
Violet turned down afree drink ?
I know, she’s
not herself.
I told you.
Thank you so much for all yoursupport
and encouragement.
Just wait, I mention you in myspeech.
To think you used to let peopleassume
you were just some dumbstripper.
Cha-ching! I have found it’sbest not to
challenge people’s assumptions
Who said a go-go boy can’t bethe hero?
I know
Hey you gonna join us onThursday at Gym Bar?
I won’t.
In fact tonight
sort of my cameo appearance.
Retirement?
What’s that about?
Come on. Sounds like you’rerunning away from home to me.
I’m doing what’s best for me.
Are you sure about this?
You wanna talk about it?
I’d love to
but it’s the pumpkin hour.
Congratulations.
6:30?
You can’t leave.
You’re gonna miss my speech.
No, you can’t leave.
Come on stay and then
Afterwards you can come back
to my place...
we’ll bake cookies, watchBeaches.
I have Kylie Karaoke.
I love Kylie Karaoke!
Well, then say yes.
I'm terrified of rejection.
Oh, you have never beenrejected!
in your life.
You have no idea.
And Zeus said you're working on
an anti-violence benefit next.
And one for the Trevor Projectafter that.
I'm impressed.
Thanks.
Yeah, Zeus is really insistentwe reach out to
straight people too, which is...
kind of intimidating since Idon't know any.
Except for Violet, but yeah...
always Violet.
This sounds like a greatopportunity.
Who knows there might be hopefor you yet.
What do you mean hope for me?
Just hope... you break out ofyour limited gay world.
Oh, that's rich coming from ahairdresser.
Hair-stylist.
Whatever. Still not much hopefor you.
Can you please stop with thegames?
You started the games.
Well, I'm through.
You want to keep playing,
play with someone else.
I often do.
Max, I just want you to knowthat you are
this close to having me.
Luke, I'm really sorry but Ican't talk now.
He is on the clock.
Oh, for Heaven sake!
Zeus
kiss me.
Luke, I am flattered.
Don't be.
Just take me homeand ravage me .
Ah Zeus, I've got issues.
Yes, you do.
You got issues too.
are we gonna be alone forever?
It depends on your definitionof alone,
doesn't it?
How long have you been in thecity now?
About 4 years.
4 years and I have never once
seen you with a boyfriend.
Nope.
You never come to my sexparties either.
You know I have poz events.
They're not my thing.
So what gets you going,big boy ?
It's way off your radar.
I wonder if you'd even treat methe same if you knew.
Two boys, one plunger.
Ewww, no.
Bartender, can I get a drink?
One second.
What happened to Violet?
She just bolted out of here.
What's going on with your BFF?
My BFF is MIA.
She is uhm
She's dating somebody.
What?
Wh...who?
Who's she dating?
Unicorn?
The mythical Uuunicorn!
Shhhh!
I'm not ready to come out yet.
Oh!
Oh you are fascinating.
Well so what? I mean myroommate is gay.
Does he have HIV?
No.
But what if he did?
Well then I'd be concerned for
your health and safety.
See, this is why weneed to mak e
HIV stigma-free.
Why shouldn't HIVhave a stigma ?
I mean it is preventable.
What about 70's high-rises andpre-
fabricated homes, they have astigma, right?
Okay, but we're talking aboutpeople.
People, not buildings.
What is wrong with you?
You're absolutely right.
I'm sorry, I'm just frustrated.
I've been after theseBiedermeier chairs
on e-bay all day.
Oh, well
If you're outbid, there'll beothers.
You're a patient man.
It's not everyday you findmatching
Beidermeier chairs on e-bay.
Where would they fit in yourapartment?
I'm shipping them back to
my folks with all the rest.
Oh, you're moving back?
Eventually.
Idaho's not really columncountry,
I'm afraid.
Bonneville is one of thefastest growing
counties in the country.
So there is plenty of work,
and I'll be renovating thehomestead.
You'd love my folks.
Would you ever consider movingback?
I kinda moved away on purpose.
Me, too.
But I look around at my friends
and co-workers and...
they don't mean much.
I think what really mattersis...
who matters.
Vern,
teach me about the Snooker
I mean the Beidermeier.
Why do you love it so?
Beidermeier is an unpretentiousclassic.
Devoid of...
unnecessary embellishment.
You can keep taking things off,you know.
Not to change the subject
but have you had cheese today?
I don't think so.
I took this tantric class
on the sacred spot massage.
Would you let me...
help you release some of thate-bay tension?
Babe, you could showLe Corbusier the
golden ratio in a Frank Gehry.
Now, just relax and trust me.
Ooops, sorry!
My bad.
Who's that?
Oh never mind, just relax.
I got 8 inches for you.
You want my 8 inches?
What, you gonna fuck me twice?
Most men hold their tension
in the pelvic floor
which is why the sacred spotmassage
is so important.
I mean it really makes you morepeaceful.
That's why you don't see the
gays marching off to war.
Who's that?
Shhhh.
Okay, here we go.
That's so wild.
It's good, ha?
Chippy likes wild.
Wild is good.
Hey, I can see you're busy
but can I borrow a condom.
Take this blindfold off.
Violet, you can't live likethis.
I gotta get you outof here now .
Come on you can stay with me.
Okay, I'll pack.
Let's just go.
Now.
Okay
Help?
Oh!
Ashley adopted in Namibia.
How was that experience?
Better than giving birth,
Actually I'm not so sure.
Africa can be notoriouslydifficult.
Joey, play nice!
So what are you writing thesedays?
No more fiction, no.
Now I write daily blogs aboutmy children.
Children?
Number two is on the way.
Darling, today blogs begin atconception.
Mommy I gotta go.
Not now.
Oh she's so cranky when she'steething.
I had to go to the doctor toget some Xanax
just to get through it.
It's your other daddy!
Hey...
Hey Matt.
How are you doing?
Where is my big boy?
Come here!
Oh, you okay?
We're fine.
I'm Markus.
Oh Markus I'm Jenny.
This is Riley's boyfriend, Imean partner.
I never know what to say.
We never know either.
Husband, actually.
Markus is my husband.
Husband, husband, husband
I want these personallydelivered
to 77 7th Avenue
My boyfriend bought it for me.
No.
What?
What's so goddamned funny?
Well, I'm notlaughing with you .
What have you manifested?
He's in your office.
Donna!
Boss?
I finally found the inspiration
for my fall line:
Bedouin tents.
Yeah?
I understand they'remildew-resistant.
Is it that hideous?
It's just... not you, is all.
Well,
Vern likes me this way
I'm gonna pretend like I didn'thear that.
I know what you're thinking.
Yeah, probably.
What if I wanna get married
and move far, far away?
What?
Audrey did it.
And I can only assume she'svery happy.
You're not Audrey.
I turned 40 this year, Riley.40!
I’m like the oldest living faghag.
Vern...
Vern might be my last chance
to settle down.
Settle just about sums it up
You are not a woman.
You do not know the pressures
I know you!
So?
So you’ve never covered up.
You’ve never ignored yourfriends.
And you told me tokill you dea d
if you ever, ever changed for aman.
You told me to kill you
if ever, ever you changed for aman.
How have I...?
Sure it's just the dog beinghousebroken?
Okay.
Okay?
-You wanna be an asshole?-I'm the asshole?
Get over there. Yes, you're theasshole.
Ah fuck you.
Fuck you!
Yeah, roll the parachute up.
Should we check with Vern?
You know I'm wearing the dress,
but I also got the balls.
Oh that's fine with mebecause...
You wanna go check with Baby?
Oh, you're on my hair!
Oww! No biting!
Ouch!
Aww! You hit me.
Bradleigh wants the camera.
Okay.. that was fucking hot.
It'd be an honor to model foryour ad
campaign Bradleigh.
It's Brad- LAY
Oh, Brad-LAY sorry.
That Marc Jacobs ad was shot inMaine.
Ocean was so icy
my junk shriveled right up!
You're new to the city I takeit?
Just got in last Friday.
We're gonna take a quick photo.
Hi, I'm Violet.
Oh, hi I'm Cyd.
But call me J-Flame...everybody does.
J-Flame?
I just realized I don't haveanything
that will fit you.
Oh, everything fits me.
I'm sample size.
True.
You got a great look.
I could use the color in my adcampaign...
or sprawled on my chinchillarug.
So lamentably the truth isyou're just too
swishy to model for Bradleigh.
Swishy?
Swishy.
But modeling only has to dowith how I look
Who told you that?
What?
Go do an email blast.
When you told me last night youloved me...
Did you mean it?
Where the hell have you been?
I haven't seen you in like aweek.
I have huge news.
What the hell are you wearing?
Vern took me shopping.
Okay. Was he the Vern?
Yes, but you know after your
rude interruption
we spent the most amazing weektogether.
And I'm not gonna say anythingelse
because I don't wanna jinx it.
Hello naked boy in my house.
I'm Andre.
I'm gonna go grab another cupof coffee.
Anybody else want?
No, thanks.
He won't leave.
You might soon be in the marketfor
a new roommate.
What do you mean? You're notleaving.
Things are movingkinda quickly .
I haven't even met Vern.
I think that's why they aregoing so great.
I also happen to know thatyou're keeping
him from Markus and Riley.
How can you be nesting withsomeone who
doesn't even know your bestfriends?
How could he possibly know you?
What's your huge news?
I found your fag stag.
Fine as fine can be...
and honey, he is into you.
I know him?
Yes!
Who?
When am I meeting Vern?
You are not.
Okay, are you ashamed of yourfriends?
Or you ashamed of yourself, ha?
I could live here.
Oh boy.
Oh Saturday afternoon is great.
Oh, I don't know.
What about you?
I'd really like to go toCentral Park.
We could stroll through therambles...
picnic at Cherry Hill
gaze at the Dakota? Mmm hmm
I prefer to wait for the light.
There's no traffic.
There's no traffic!
It's one of the ways I practicepatience.
Oh for Pete's sake.
What are you gonna do with me?
Practice patience.
Lot of men checking you out.
Oh hi Violet!
Women, too. Are you famous?
Look. Gargoyle!
What in the world is going onhere?
I totally forgot that this lawnis a...
boy-hive.
Vern, I am afraid thatsomething is
about to go down
and I need to tell you.
What is it? You can tell meanything.
Remember my roommate?
I was blindfolded at the time.
He's just the tip of...you kno w
all my life I've been a fruitfly.
What?
Fag hag? Queen mother?
Every last man in my life isgay.
We'll get through this.
Vernon, run!
No, wait!
What is going on here?
This is an intervention.
Just give me a minute.
No, please. We wanthim to stay .
Who are you people?
We're her friends
More than friends.
In a totally not sexual way,but
This is us at our first pride,remember that?
You've always beenunconditional...
and we support you no matter
who you choose to love.
But your heterosexuality ishurting us
in the following ways:
Since you met Vern it feelslike you're
becoming someone who's notViolet.
How dare you say I'm not goodfor Violet.
Honestly, it's not about you.
It's about her.
Vern, no.
Wait!
I haven't even read mine yet.
We just wanna be part of yourlife.
I knew this was a bad idea.
Free hugs!
Free hug.
What?!?
You know surrogates are reallyhard
to come by.
Yes And expensive.
The best deal is this agency inIndia.
Really?
Yeah.
You give them 20 grand, flydown there
with the egg and the sperm
9 months later fly back
and pick up your newborn.
Can't they just Fed-Ex the babyback?
Well, Riley and I were thinkingabout
going the Polynesian route.
You know Peter and I are gonnado that for our next one.
You two shouldreally look into .
You might get a two-for-onespecial.
Oh yeah.
Are you okay, sweetie?
Are you okay?
What's going on?
You alright?
Just breathe.
Like Lamaze breathing...
like that.
Maybe we should have heard themout.
Why?
We have each other now.
My friends aren’t placeholders.
I'm not sure I like yourfriends.
You're gonna have to give them
another shot.
Seems like you don't like themmuch either.
Well, you're wrong.I love them .
Remember what you said?
They are who matters...
to me.
Well, that's a shame because Ithought
I'd be the one that mattered toyou.
Well of course you do.
I've got a proposal for you.
These are the renovations to my
homestead in Idaho.
Outside Idaho Falls.
I hired a contractor and Iwanted you to see
the plans to see if youapproved.
It's a Victorian...
lots of acreage,
fresh air.
Aren't your parentsstill there ?
It's 5000 square feet...
and my folks...
my folks would adore you.
Look... here's my dad.
I'm sure I'd love them.
I just don't know if this isthe life for Violet
And I got plane tickets.
for the end of November.
You got plane tickets?
You didn't ask me.
Will you go?
Well, I'm going to Taiwan
with Bradleigh in November.
I'm sure they'll let you offwork
It's only couple of weeks
and if they don't...
I make enough for two.
I'd like the façade to stayoriginal
you know how sentimental I am
about architecture
but the interior needs to betotally gutted.
You have this whole thingworked out,
don't you?
They are just plans. They canchange.
What about my life here?
We'd start a whole new life.
Why in the world would I wannado that?
Idaho?
You're kidding?
There's like one decent gay barin Idaho.
What are you saying Violet?
You're scaring me
And it's in Pocatello!
I'm not a simple girl.
I'm a complex, subversive woman
and I can't pretend anymorethat I'm not.
Vern, I have totallymisrepresented myself.
Stop. What did I do?
What did I say?
Nothing.
Sweet Vern, I'm so sorry.
It's not you... it's me.
I love you.
What did you just say?
I said I love you.
What's my name?
I am so in love with you.
Okay
I think you need to go.
But I love you.
Yeah.
You gotta go.
Hello?
I'm sorry I couldn't tell youbefore but I love you
Do you hear me?
Me too.
And I know sucking every lastcock in
the city is not the best way toshow you
but I am madly in love with youDarian.
It's Dad.
What?
Luke, this is your father.
Oh my god, wrong number.
You have 473 newFrisky Friends .
I love you.
I feel like I'm stuck inA Small World.
Hostage on a boat with allthose little
Dutch kids singing
Okay.
I hate this ride.
Then let's get off it for awhile.
There are other rides, you know
I know Riley...
I know.
We don't have to keep goinground
and round on the same old one.
No, no we don't. We can have itall.
Now if you'd just get out ofthe playpen
So, what'd you really thinkabout Vern?
I wouldn't kick him out of bed.
That's not saying a whole lot.
Oh my gosh, did you hear whathappened
last night between Riley andMarkus?
No.
I got the craziest text.
What now?
We'll just wait and look at iton the
blog but you know
same old, same old.
Wow.
How long have those two beentogether?
I don't know, like 50 years.
Yesterday was a disaster on allcounts.
Hey, do you ever just think ofjust like,
I don't know quittingeverything and
going back to school orsomething?
School? What would we study?
You mean like choose a major?
Yeah, choose a major.
I'm still undecided.
Me too.
Pull out all the stops. I wantthe works.
You got it.
I'm working Luke's sex partytonight
and this weekend is mydebutante ball
where I will be formallyreintroduced
into gay society.
You're coming right?
Absolutely.
How is Luke?
He's fine.
He drunk dialed his dad.
Sounds right.
He meant to drunk dial you.
If only he wasn't so stubborn,
so sarcastic.
Luke has his problems.
He's so infuriating.
And yet...
he's the only person I want towake up with.
I do not understand why twopeople who
have so much in common
just wanna pick each otherapart all the time.
You're gonna end up two bitterold queens
and lord knows we've enough ofthose.
Does this necklace make me lookfat?
Oh come on. I've missed you.
-I missed you too.-Alright.
Does it make melook fat though?
No.
Okay, good.
I need to see your penis.
I love this job.
Uncut.
Like a little calamari.
Thanks.
Penis please.
Grower?
Bottom.
Hey sweetie. Thanks
Hey babe.
Go on in.
Don't you need to see my dick?
I'm pretty sure you're not thepolice.
Don't you want to?
Go in.
She's not getting it bro.
Violet, I told him you'd behere.
I'm setting you up. Hello!?
Fag stag.
But you... sexy dance for men.
You love Bette Midler,
your favorite movie is Beaches.
Oh my god
You are making me blush.
I don't think I've blushedbefore.
Alright you guys.
Take it into the back,
I will take over from here.
Hey there.
40 dollars and yourdick please .
What the fuck?
Eww
They got breeders back there.
I only threw up a little bitLuke.
Guys I'm just bringing queerstogether.
Yeah, queers.
Split me like a wishbone!
Okay, that's...
that's pretty queer.
That's our Violet.
Excuse me, do you have a minute
for the children?
How you doing?
You don't have my keys anymorebut...
I still have yours.
Darian, I love you.
I do, I love you.
Luke.
What?
It's not gonna suck itself.
Maybe this time around weshouldn't
begin with a blow job.
Hey there.
I knew you were coming.
Actually, I'm here to seeViolet.
These aren't for me?
No.
Violet. you have a visitor.
Sorry for the mix up. Youunderstand.
Hey, how you doing sweetie?
Good!
These are for you.
Thank you very much.
I thought I'd pop in andsurprise invite
you to lunch.
I'm going to lunch with Rileyand Markus.
Couples counseling.
Oh, okay.
Wanna have dinner?
Sure, great.
Maybe we can all get togetherand
do something after?
Yes, and you'll be at mydeb. ball, yeah?
With bells on.
Just bells, right?
Right.
Okay well... give the boys ahug from me.
I will, I'll call you later.
Yeah. Please do.
I'll go to lunch with him.
You don't eat.
I could learn.
Where did you find him?
Gay sex club.
Don't be ridiculous.
How is that possible?
Well
I'd tell you, but Salome
I just don't think you'recoachable.
Come on, I gotta piss.
Guys!How is it going?
Good. They're in loveand I'm here with my baby.
Waaa!
A very colicky baby.
Still sleeping in the playpen?
My life is an open blog.
I'm sorry, he just needed alittle fluff.
Thank you for the poppers.
Hey, hey...debutante!
It's been ages.
It has. I'm thrilledto be back .
Ah! I can't believehe wants me .
Violet, modesty has neversuited you.
That's true and I love it.
I love that you guysare finall y
slobbering over my man.
I've already installed ananny-cam
in your bedroom.
It's the best sexI've ever had .
Oh my goodness. And it's notjust the sex
we have this spark.
Well, it's not just the sex.
Darian, what have you done withLuke?
I don't know.
But he's trying to steamroll me
into monogamy.
No I am not!
So Violet how does it feel tobe back?
Feels so good to be home.
And if and when youtwo get you r
bundle of joy
you better make me the fairygodmother.
Honey, you already are.
Get the fuck out of my way.
Donna what are you doing here?
Slumming.
Hey, its Next Magazine.
Zeus, get over here.
Paparazzi, no photos.
I beseech you, no photos!